export const extendedCryptoObject = [
  {
    id: "bitcoin",
    allTimeHigh: "73500",
    moreInformation:
      "Bitcoin (BTC) is the first and most well-known cryptocurrency, created by an unknown person or group of people using the pseudonym Satoshi Nakamoto in 2008. It operates on a decentralized network called blockchain, which is secured by cryptographic principles. Bitcoin's primary use case is as a digital currency for peer-to-peer transactions, but it has also gained popularity as a store of value and a hedge against inflation.",
    moreInformation2:
      "Bitcoin's decentralized nature means that no single entity controls it, making it resistant to censorship and manipulation. Transactions on the Bitcoin network are verified by network nodes through cryptography and recorded on a public ledger called a blockchain. Bitcoin mining, the process of adding new transactions to the blockchain, is carried out by miners who compete to solve complex mathematical puzzles.",
    frequentlyAskedQuestions: [
      {
        question: "What is Bitcoin?",
        answer:
          "Bitcoin (BTC) is the first decentralized digital currency, created in 2009 by an unknown person or group of people using the pseudonym Satoshi Nakamoto.",
      },
      {
        question: "Who created Bitcoin?",
        answer:
          "Bitcoin (BTC) was created by an unknown person or group of people using the pseudonym Satoshi Nakamoto.",
      },
      {
        question: "How can I buy Bitcoin?",
        answer:
          "Bitcoin (BTC) can be purchased on various cryptocurrency exchanges and platforms that support its trading.",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: "ethereum",
    allTimeHigh: "4800",
    moreInformation:
      "Ethereum (ETH) is a decentralized platform that enables the creation and execution of smart contracts and decentralized applications (DApps). It was proposed by Vitalik Buterin in late 2013 and development began in early 2014, with the network going live on July 30, 2015. Ethereum's native cryptocurrency, Ether (ETH), is used to pay for transaction fees and computational services on the network.",
    moreInformation2:
      "Ethereum's smart contract functionality allows developers to build applications that run exactly as programmed without any downtime, censorship, fraud, or third-party interference. This has led to the emergence of a wide range of decentralized applications across various industries, including decentralized finance (DeFi), non-fungible tokens (NFTs), gaming, and supply chain management.",
    frequentlyAskedQuestions: [
      {
        question: "What is Ethereum?",
        answer:
          "Ethereum (ETH) is a decentralized platform that enables developers to build and deploy smart contracts and decentralized applications (DApps).",
      },
      {
        question: "Who created Ethereum?",
        answer:
          "Ethereum (ETH) was proposed by Vitalik Buterin in late 2013 and development was crowdfunded in 2014.",
      },
      {
        question: "How can I develop on Ethereum?",
        answer:
          "Developers can build and deploy smart contracts and decentralized applications (DApps) on the Ethereum (ETH) platform using programming languages like Solidity.",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: "tether",
    allTimeHigh: "1.21",
    moreInformation:
      "Tether (USDT) is a type of cryptocurrency known as a stablecoin, designed to maintain a stable value by pegging it to a fiat currency, such as the US dollar, at a 1:1 ratio. It was originally launched in 2014 as Realcoin and later rebranded as Tether in 2015. Tether aims to combine the benefits of cryptocurrencies, such as fast transactions and borderless transferability, with the stability of traditional fiat currencies.",
    moreInformation2:
      "Tether tokens are issued on various blockchain networks, including Bitcoin (Omni Layer), Ethereum (ERC-20), Tron (TRC-20), and others. Each USDT token is backed by a reserve of fiat currency held in Tether's reserves, which undergo regular audits to ensure transparency and stability. Tether is widely used as a means of transferring value between different cryptocurrency exchanges and as a hedge against market volatility.",
    frequentlyAskedQuestions: [
      {
        question: "What is Tether?",
        answer:
          "Tether (USDT) is a type of cryptocurrency known as a stablecoin, designed to maintain a stable value by pegging it to a fiat currency like the US dollar.",
      },
      {
        question: "How is Tether backed?",
        answer:
          "Tether (USDT) is typically backed by a reserve of fiat currency held by the issuing company.",
      },
      {
        question: "Where can I use Tether?",
        answer:
          "Tether (USDT) is widely used for trading and as a medium of exchange on cryptocurrency exchanges and platforms.",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: "binance-coin",
    allTimeHigh: "690",
    moreInformation:
      "BNB (BNB) is the native cryptocurrency of the Binance exchange, one of the largest cryptocurrency exchanges in the world by trading volume. It was launched through an initial coin offering (ICO) in July 2017, with the aim of powering the Binance ecosystem and incentivizing users to trade on the platform. BNB initially operated as an ERC-20 token on the Ethereum blockchain but later migrated to Binance's own blockchain, Binance Chain.",
    moreInformation2:
      "BNB has multiple use cases within the Binance ecosystem, including paying for trading fees, participating in token sales, and accessing various features on the Binance platform. Binance also periodically burns a portion of BNB tokens from circulation, reducing the total supply over time and potentially increasing its value. Additionally, BNB is used to power Binance Smart Chain, a parallel blockchain that enables the creation of decentralized applications (DApps) and smart contracts.",
    frequentlyAskedQuestions: [
      {
        question: "What is Binance Coin?",
        answer:
          "Binance Coin (BNB) is the native cryptocurrency of the Binance exchange, one of the largest cryptocurrency exchanges in the world.",
      },
      {
        question: "How can I use Binance Coin?",
        answer:
          "Binance Coin (BNB) can be used for various purposes on the Binance exchange, including trading, paying for transaction fees, and participating in token sales.",
      },
      {
        question: "What is Binance Smart Chain?",
        answer:
          "Binance Smart Chain (BSC) is a blockchain platform developed by Binance, offering smart contract functionality and compatibility with Ethereum Virtual Machine (EVM).",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: "solana",
    allTimeHigh: "260",
    moreInformation:
      "Solana (SOL) is a high-performance blockchain platform designed for decentralized applications (DApps) and crypto projects. It aims to provide fast, secure, and scalable solutions for developers to build decentralized applications and create new digital assets. Solana utilizes a unique combination of technologies, including a proof-of-history (PoH) consensus mechanism, to achieve high throughput and low latency.",
    moreInformation2:
      "With its ability to handle thousands of transactions per second and sub-second transaction finality, Solana offers a compelling platform for applications requiring high performance and reliability. Developers can leverage Solana's flexible architecture and developer-friendly tools to create innovative DApps across various industries, including decentralized finance (DeFi), non-fungible tokens (NFTs), and gaming.",
    frequentlyAskedQuestions: [
      {
        question: "What is Solana?",
        answer:
          "Solana (SOL) is a high-performance blockchain platform designed for decentralized applications (DApps) and crypto projects.",
      },
      {
        question: "How does Solana achieve scalability?",
        answer:
          "Solana (SOL) achieves scalability through its unique consensus mechanism called Proof of History (PoH) combined with Proof of Stake (PoS), enabling fast and low-cost transactions.",
      },
      {
        question: "What are some projects built on Solana?",
        answer:
          "There are various projects and decentralized applications (DApps) built on Solana (SOL), including decentralized finance (DeFi) platforms, non-fungible token (NFT) marketplaces, and gaming applications.",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: "usd-coin",
    allTimeHigh: "1.15",
    moreInformation:
      "USDC (USDC) is a stablecoin pegged to the US dollar on a 1:1 basis, meaning that one USDC token is always equivalent to one US dollar. It was launched in 2018 as a joint venture between Circle and Coinbase and has since gained widespread adoption in the cryptocurrency ecosystem. USDC is widely used for trading, lending, remittances, and other applications where a stable store of value is required.",
    moreInformation2:
      " As a regulated and audited stablecoin, USDC offers transparency, reliability, and liquidity to users and businesses operating in the digital asset space. With its seamless integration into various cryptocurrency exchanges, wallets, and DeFi protocols, USDC plays a vital role in facilitating liquidity and stability within the crypto economy.",
    frequentlyAskedQuestions: [
      {
        question: "What is USD Coin?",
        answer:
          "USD Coin (USDC) is a type of cryptocurrency known as a stablecoin, designed to maintain a stable value by pegging it to the US dollar.",
      },
      {
        question: "How is USD Coin different from Tether?",
        answer:
          "USD Coin (USDC) is backed by a reserve of US dollars held in custody by regulated financial institutions, while Tether (USDT) is backed by a mix of fiat currency reserves and other assets.",
      },
      {
        question: "Where can I use USD Coin?",
        answer:
          "USD Coin (USDC) is widely used for trading, as a medium of exchange, and as a stable store of value on various cryptocurrency exchanges and platforms.",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: "xrp",
    allTimeHigh: "3.84",
    moreInformation:
      "XRP (XRP) is a digital asset and cryptocurrency designed for fast and low-cost cross-border payments. It was created by Ripple Labs in 2012 with the aim of enabling real-time, secure, and inexpensive international money transfers. XRP operates on a decentralized network of validators and utilizes a consensus algorithm called the XRP Ledger (XRPL) to process transactions quickly and efficiently.",
    moreInformation2:
      " With its focus on facilitating efficient cross-border payments, XRP has garnered interest from financial institutions and remittance companies seeking to reduce settlement times and transaction costs. Additionally, XRP's consensus mechanism and scalable architecture make it suitable for a wide range of applications beyond payments, including tokenized assets and decentralized finance (DeFi).",
    frequentlyAskedQuestions: [
      {
        question: "What is XRP?",
        answer:
          "XRP is the native cryptocurrency of the Ripple network, a digital payment protocol that enables fast and low-cost cross-border transactions.",
      },
      {
        question: "How does XRP differ from Bitcoin?",
        answer:
          "XRP operates on a different consensus mechanism called the Ripple Protocol Consensus Algorithm (RPCA), which allows for faster transaction confirmation and lower fees compared to Bitcoin.",
      },
      {
        question: "What is RippleNet?",
        answer:
          "RippleNet is a network of financial institutions and payment providers that use Ripple's technology to facilitate cross-border payments and remittances.",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: "dogecoin",
    allTimeHigh: "0.7",
    moreInformation:
      "Dogecoin (DOGE) is a peer-to-peer cryptocurrency created as a lighthearted joke based on the popular 'Doge' meme in 2013. Despite its origins, Dogecoin has developed a strong community and has been used for various charitable causes and tipping on social media platforms. Dogecoin's transaction speed and low fees make it suitable for microtransactions and everyday use cases. Dogecoin's community-driven approach and vibrant community have contributed to its longevity and continued relevance in the cryptocurrency space.",
    frequentlyAskedQuestions: [
      {
        question: "What is Dogecoin?",
        answer:
          "Dogecoin (DOGE) is a cryptocurrency created as a joke in 2013, featuring the Shiba Inu dog from the 'Doge' meme as its logo.",
      },
      {
        question: "Who created Dogecoin?",
        answer:
          "Dogecoin (DOGE) was created by software engineers Billy Markus and Jackson Palmer as a lighthearted alternative to Bitcoin.",
      },
      {
        question: "What is the use of Dogecoin?",
        answer:
          "Dogecoin (DOGE) is primarily used for tipping content creators and charitable donations, as well as trading and speculation.",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: "cardano",
    allTimeHigh: "3.1",
    moreInformation:
      "Cardano (ADA) is a decentralized platform that aims to provide a more secure and scalable infrastructure for the development and deployment of smart contracts and decentralized applications (DApps). It was founded by Charles Hoskinson, one of the co-founders of Ethereum, and launched in 2017 after a successful ICO.",
    moreInformation2:
      "Cardano's unique approach to blockchain architecture aims to address the scalability, interoperability, and sustainability challenges faced by existing blockchain platforms. With its focus on formal verification, layered architecture, and consensus mechanism, Cardano seeks to offer a more robust and resilient platform for building decentralized applications across various industries.",
    frequentlyAskedQuestions: [
      {
        question: "What is Cardano?",
        answer:
          "Cardano (ADA) is a blockchain platform that aims to provide a more secure and scalable infrastructure for the development and deployment of decentralized applications (DApps) and smart contracts.",
      },
      {
        question: "How does Cardano achieve scalability?",
        answer:
          "Cardano (ADA) achieves scalability through its layered architecture, allowing for separate computation and settlement layers, as well as its consensus algorithm called Ouroboros.",
      },
      {
        question: "What is the difference between Cardano and Ethereum?",
        answer:
          "Cardano (ADA) aims to address some of the scalability and sustainability issues faced by Ethereum, with a focus on formal verification and interoperability.",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: "shiba-inu",
    allTimeHigh: "0.00003",
    moreInformation:
      "Shiba Inu (SHIB) is a meme-based cryptocurrency inspired by the Shiba Inu dog breed, similar to Dogecoin. It was created in August 2020 as an experiment in decentralized community building and has since gained significant attention and adoption. Shiba Inu aims to replicate the success of Dogecoin and has attracted a large following on social media platforms like Twitter and Reddit.",
    moreInformation2:
      "Despite its humorous origins, Shiba Inu has developed a vibrant community and ecosystem, with projects and initiatives spanning decentralized finance (DeFi), non-fungible tokens (NFTs), and charitable causes. With its enthusiastic community and growing ecosystem, Shiba Inu continues to capture the imagination of cryptocurrency enthusiasts worldwide.",
    frequentlyAskedQuestions: [
      {
        question: "What is Shiba Inu?",
        answer:
          "Shiba Inu (SHIB) is a cryptocurrency created as an experiment in decentralized community building.",
      },
      {
        question: "Who created Shiba Inu?",
        answer:
          "Shiba Inu (SHIB) was created anonymously by a person or group of people using the pseudonym 'Ryoshi.'",
      },
      {
        question: "What is the use of Shiba Inu?",
        answer:
          "Shiba Inu (SHIB) is primarily used for trading and speculation, as well as community engagement through its decentralized ecosystem.",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: "avalanche",
    allTimeHigh: "150",
    moreInformation:
      "Avalanche (AVAX) is a decentralized platform that aims to provide an open, programmable framework for building and deploying decentralized applications (DApps) and custom blockchain networks. It was founded by Ava Labs in 2018 and launched its mainnet in September 2020.",
    moreInformation2:
      "Avalanche utilizes a unique consensus mechanism called Avalanche consensus, which enables high throughput, low latency, and customizable blockchain networks. With its focus on scalability, interoperability, and security, Avalanche offers a compelling platform for developers to create innovative DApps across various industries, including decentralized finance (DeFi), asset tokenization, and supply chain management.",
    frequentlyAskedQuestions: [
      {
        question: "What is Avalanche?",
        answer:
          "Avalanche (AVAX) is a blockchain platform that aims to provide a highly scalable and customizable infrastructure for decentralized applications (DApps) and financial assets.",
      },
      {
        question: "How does Avalanche achieve scalability?",
        answer:
          "Avalanche (AVAX) achieves scalability through its novel consensus protocol called Avalanche consensus, which allows for rapid and secure transaction processing.",
      },
      {
        question: "What are some use cases for Avalanche?",
        answer:
          "Avalanche (AVAX) is used for various use cases, including decentralized finance (DeFi), asset tokenization, and enterprise applications.",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: "tron",
    allTimeHigh: "0.3",
    moreInformation:
      "TRON (TRX) is a blockchain-based platform that aims to decentralize the internet by providing a decentralized infrastructure for content creation, distribution, and consumption. It was founded by Justin Sun in 2017 and launched its mainnet in 2018. TRON aims to disrupt the digital entertainment industry by enabling content creators to directly monetize their content without intermediaries.",
    moreInformation2:
      "With its high throughput, low latency, and scalability, TRON offers a compelling platform for developers to build decentralized applications (DApps) across various verticals, including gaming, social media, and content streaming.",
    frequentlyAskedQuestions: [
      {
        question: "What is TRON?",
        answer:
          "TRON (TRX) is a blockchain platform that aims to create a decentralized internet ecosystem by providing infrastructure for decentralized applications (DApps) and content distribution.",
      },
      {
        question: "Who founded TRON?",
        answer:
          "TRON (TRX) was founded by Justin Sun, a prominent figure in the cryptocurrency and blockchain space.",
      },
      {
        question: "What are some DApps built on TRON?",
        answer:
          "There are various decentralized applications (DApps) built on TRON (TRX), including gaming platforms, decentralized exchanges (DEXs), and social media applications.",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: "wrapped-bitcoin",
    allTimeHigh: "80000",
    moreInformation:
      "Wrapped Bitcoin (WBTC) is an Ethereum-based token that represents a 1:1 pegged version of Bitcoin (BTC). It was created to bring Bitcoin's liquidity and value to the Ethereum ecosystem, allowing users to access decentralized finance (DeFi) applications and smart contracts using Bitcoin.",
    moreInformation2:
      " WBTC tokens are backed by Bitcoin held in reserve by custodians and can be minted and redeemed on a 1:1 basis through a network of approved merchants and custodians. With its interoperability and liquidity benefits, WBTC has become a popular asset in the Ethereum DeFi ecosystem, enabling users to access a wide range of financial services using Bitcoin.",
    frequentlyAskedQuestions: [
      {
        question: "What is Wrapped Bitcoin?",
        answer:
          "Wrapped Bitcoin (WBTC) is a tokenized version of Bitcoin (BTC) that runs on the Ethereum blockchain.",
      },
      {
        question: "How can I convert Bitcoin to Wrapped Bitcoin?",
        answer:
          "Bitcoin can be converted to Wrapped Bitcoin (WBTC) through approved custodians and decentralized exchanges (DEXs) that support tokenization.",
      },
      {
        question: "What are some use cases for Wrapped Bitcoin?",
        answer:
          "Wrapped Bitcoin (WBTC) is used for various decentralized finance (DeFi) applications, including lending, borrowing, and trading on Ethereum-based platforms.",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: "polkadot",
    allTimeHigh: "50",
    moreInformation:
      "Polkadot (DOT) is a decentralized platform that aims to enable the interoperability and scalability of blockchains. It was founded by Dr. Gavin Wood, one of the co-founders of Ethereum, and launched its mainnet in 2020. Polkadot utilizes a unique relay chain and parachain architecture to facilitate cross-chain communication and scalability.",
    moreInformation2:
      " With its focus on interoperability, Polkadot enables different blockchains to connect and share information, assets, and functionalities, creating a more connected and efficient blockchain ecosystem. With its innovative technology and growing ecosystem of projects and developers, Polkadot is poised to play a key role in the future of blockchain technology.",
    frequentlyAskedQuestions: [
      {
        question: "What is Polkadot?",
        answer:
          "Polkadot (DOT) is a multi-chain blockchain platform that enables interoperability between different blockchains.",
      },
      {
        question: "How does Polkadot achieve interoperability?",
        answer:
          "Polkadot (DOT) achieves interoperability through its relay chain and parachain architecture, allowing for cross-chain communication and data transfer.",
      },
      {
        question: "What are parachains?",
        answer:
          "Parachains are individual blockchains that connect to the Polkadot (DOT) network, enabling them to interact with other parachains and the Polkadot relay chain.",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: "bitcoin-cash",
    allTimeHigh: "4000",
    moreInformation:
      "Bitcoin Cash (BCH) is a peer-to-peer electronic cash system that aims to enable fast, low-cost transactions for everyday use. It was created in 2017 as a fork of Bitcoin (BTC) with the goal of improving scalability and transaction throughput.",
    moreInformation2:
      " Bitcoin Cash utilizes a larger block size compared to Bitcoin, allowing for more transactions to be processed per block. With its focus on usability and accessibility, Bitcoin Cash aims to provide a seamless experience for users to send and receive payments without the need for intermediaries. With its growing adoption and community support, Bitcoin Cash continues to evolve as a viable alternative to traditional payment systems.",
    frequentlyAskedQuestions: [
      {
        question: "What is Bitcoin Cash?",
        answer:
          "Bitcoin Cash (BCH) is a peer-to-peer electronic cash system that aims to enable fast and low-cost transactions.",
      },
      {
        question: "How does Bitcoin Cash differ from Bitcoin?",
        answer:
          "Bitcoin Cash (BCH) has a larger block size limit compared to Bitcoin (BTC), allowing for more transactions to be processed per block and lower fees.",
      },
      {
        question: "What is the future of Bitcoin Cash?",
        answer:
          "The future of Bitcoin Cash (BCH) depends on its adoption as a means of payment and store of value, as well as its ability to address scalability and security concerns.",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: "chainlink",
    allTimeHigh: "60",
    moreInformation:
      "Chainlink (LINK) is a decentralized oracle network that aims to connect smart contracts with real-world data. It was founded by Sergey Nazarov and Steve Ellis in 2017 and launched its mainnet in 2019. Chainlink enables smart contracts to securely interact with external data sources, APIs, and payment systems, making it possible to create decentralized applications (DApps) with real-world functionality.",
    moreInformation2:
      "With its decentralized architecture and robust security features, Chainlink provides a reliable and tamper-proof solution for bringing off-chain data onto the blockchain. As a result, Chainlink has gained widespread adoption across various industries, including finance, insurance, supply chain management, and gaming.",
    frequentlyAskedQuestions: [
      {
        question: "What is Chainlink?",
        answer:
          "Chainlink (LINK) is a decentralized oracle network that aims to connect smart contracts with real-world data.",
      },
      {
        question: "How does Chainlink work?",
        answer:
          "Chainlink (LINK) uses a network of independent node operators, called oracles, to retrieve and verify real-world data and deliver it to smart contracts on the blockchain.",
      },
      {
        question: "What are some use cases for Chainlink?",
        answer:
          "Chainlink (LINK) is used for various use cases, including decentralized finance (DeFi), insurance, gaming, and supply chain management.",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: "near-protocol",
    allTimeHigh: "20",
    moreInformation:
      "NEAR Protocol (NEAR) is a decentralized platform that aims to enable the development and deployment of scalable and secure decentralized applications (DApps). It was founded by Alex Skidanov and Illia Polosukhin in 2018 and launched its mainnet in 2020. NEAR Protocol utilizes a unique sharding mechanism called Nightshade to achieve high throughput and low latency, making it suitable for applications requiring fast and cost-effective transactions.",
    moreInformation2:
      " With its focus on developer-friendly tools and infrastructure, NEAR Protocol aims to lower the barriers to entry for building decentralized applications, enabling developers to innovate and create new use cases across various industries. With its growing ecosystem of projects and partnerships, NEAR Protocol is poised to play a significant role in the future of decentralized technology.",
    frequentlyAskedQuestions: [
      {
        question: "What is NEAR Protocol?",
        answer:
          "NEAR Protocol (NEAR) is a decentralized platform that aims to enable the creation and deployment of scalable and user-friendly decentralized applications (DApps).",
      },
      {
        question: "How does NEAR Protocol achieve scalability?",
        answer:
          "NEAR Protocol (NEAR) achieves scalability through its use of sharding, a technique that divides the network into smaller groups of nodes (shards) to process transactions in parallel.",
      },
      {
        question: "What programming languages can I use for NEAR development?",
        answer:
          "Developers can build decentralized applications (DApps) on NEAR Protocol (NEAR) using languages like Rust and AssemblyScript.",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: "polygon",
    allTimeHigh: "3.5",
    moreInformation:
      "Polygon (MATIC) is a scalable and interoperable blockchain platform that aims to address the scalability challenges faced by Ethereum. It was founded by Jaynti Kanani and Sandeep Nailwal in 2017 and launched its mainnet in 2020. Polygon utilizes a Layer 2 scaling solution called Plasma to enable fast and low-cost transactions on the Ethereum network.",
    moreInformation2:
      " With its focus on interoperability and compatibility with Ethereum, Polygon offers a seamless transition for developers and users looking to migrate to a scalable blockchain solution. With its growing ecosystem of decentralized applications (DApps) and protocols, Polygon provides a vibrant platform for building and deploying decentralized finance (DeFi), non-fungible tokens (NFTs), and gaming applications.",
    frequentlyAskedQuestions: [
      {
        question: "What is Polygon?",
        answer:
          "Polygon (MATIC) is a protocol and framework for building and connecting Ethereum-compatible blockchain networks.",
      },
      {
        question: "How does Polygon improve Ethereum scalability?",
        answer:
          "Polygon (MATIC) improves Ethereum scalability by providing solutions like sidechains, which can process transactions faster and at lower costs compared to the Ethereum mainnet.",
      },
      {
        question: "What are some projects built on Polygon?",
        answer:
          "There are various decentralized applications (DApps) and projects built on Polygon (MATIC), including decentralized finance (DeFi) platforms, non-fungible token (NFT) marketplaces, and gaming applications.",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: "litecoin",
    allTimeHigh: "400",
    moreInformation:
      "Litecoin (LTC) is a peer-to-peer cryptocurrency created by Charlie Lee in 2011 as a fork of the Bitcoin Core client. It was designed to offer faster transaction confirmation times and a different hashing algorithm (scrypt) than Bitcoin. Litecoin's blockchain aims to process a block every 2.5 minutes on average, compared to Bitcoin's 10 minutes, making it suitable for smaller transactions and everyday use. With its focus on speed and efficiency, Litecoin has become known as the 'silver to Bitcoin's gold' and has gained popularity as a payment method for goods and services.",
    moreInformation2:
      "In addition to its fast transaction times, Litecoin also offers lower transaction fees compared to Bitcoin, making it an attractive option for users looking to send funds quickly and affordably. Litecoin has a capped supply of 84 million coins, four times the supply of Bitcoin, which may provide additional scarcity and value over time. With its active development community, strong network security, and widespread adoption, Litecoin continues to be one of the leading cryptocurrencies in terms of market capitalization and user acceptance.",
    frequentlyAskedQuestions: [
      {
        question: "What is Litecoin?",
        answer:
          "Litecoin (LTC) is a peer-to-peer cryptocurrency created by Charlie Lee in 2011. It is often referred to as the silver to Bitcoin's gold and was designed to provide fast and low-cost transactions.",
      },
      {
        question: "Who created Litecoin?",
        answer:
          "Litecoin (LTC) was created by Charlie Lee, a former Google employee and software engineer.",
      },
      {
        question: "How does Litecoin differ from Bitcoin?",
        answer:
          "Litecoin (LTC) uses a different hashing algorithm (Scrypt) and has a faster block generation time compared to Bitcoin (BTC), resulting in quicker transaction confirmations.",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: "internet-computer",
    allTimeHigh: "700",
    moreInformation:
      "Internet Computer (ICP) is a decentralized platform that aims to provide a secure and scalable environment for hosting web content and applications without reliance on traditional web infrastructure. It was founded by the DFINITY Foundation and launched its mainnet in 2021. Internet Computer utilizes a unique consensus mechanism called Threshold Relay to achieve high throughput and fast finality, making it suitable for hosting scalable and tamper-resistant applications.",
    moreInformation2:
      "With its focus on decentralization and censorship resistance, Internet Computer aims to democratize access to the internet and empower developers to create a new generation of decentralized web applications. With its innovative technology and ambitious vision, Internet Computer has garnered significant attention and adoption within the blockchain community.",
    frequentlyAskedQuestions: [
      {
        question: "What is Internet Computer?",
        answer:
          "Internet Computer (ICP) is a blockchain project developed by the DFINITY Foundation. It aims to create a decentralized computing platform that enables the development and deployment of internet-scale software and services directly on the blockchain.",
      },
      {
        question: "Who developed Internet Computer?",
        answer:
          "Internet Computer (ICP) was developed by the DFINITY Foundation, a Swiss-based non-profit organization.",
      },
      {
        question: "What is the purpose of Internet Computer?",
        answer:
          "The purpose of Internet Computer (ICP) is to provide a decentralized platform for building and running secure and scalable internet-scale applications without the need for traditional IT infrastructure.",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: "unus-sed-leo",
    allTimeHigh: "3.89",
    moreInformation:
      "UNUS SED LEO (LEO) is a utility token issued by Bitfinex, one of the world's largest cryptocurrency exchanges. It is designed to provide various benefits to users of the Bitfinex platform, including discounts on trading fees, enhanced liquidity, and access to exclusive features and services. LEO tokens can be used for trading, staking, and participation in platform governance.",
    moreInformation2:
      "As a native token of Bitfinex, LEO plays a crucial role in the ecosystem by incentivizing platform usage and promoting user engagement. With its robust utility and growing adoption, LEO has become an integral part of the cryptocurrency trading landscape.",
    frequentlyAskedQuestions: [
      {
        question: "What is UNUS SED LEO?",
        answer:
          "UNUS SED LEO (LEO) is a utility token issued by Bitfinex, providing various benefits and privileges to users of the Bitfinex platform.",
      },
      {
        question: "How can I use UNUS SED LEO?",
        answer:
          "LEO tokens can be used for trading, staking, and participation in platform governance on the Bitfinex exchange.",
      },
      {
        question: "What are the benefits of holding UNUS SED LEO?",
        answer:
          "Holding LEO tokens provides users with discounts on trading fees, enhanced liquidity, and access to exclusive features and services on the Bitfinex platform.",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: "dai",
    allTimeHigh: "1.38",
    moreInformation:
      "Dai (DAI) is a decentralized stablecoin pegged to the value of the US dollar. It is created and managed by the MakerDAO decentralized autonomous organization (DAO) through a system of smart contracts on the Ethereum blockchain. Dai maintains its stability through over-collateralization of assets and an algorithmic stabilization mechanism.",
    moreInformation2:
      "As a decentralized stablecoin, Dai offers users a censorship-resistant, borderless, and programmable form of digital money. It can be used for payments, remittances, lending, and other decentralized finance (DeFi) applications.",
    frequentlyAskedQuestions: [
      {
        question: "What is Dai?",
        answer:
          "Dai (DAI) is a decentralized stablecoin pegged to the value of the US dollar, created and managed by the MakerDAO decentralized autonomous organization.",
      },
      {
        question: "How is Dai different from other stablecoins?",
        answer:
          "Dai maintains its stability through a decentralized system of smart contracts and over-collateralization of assets, making it more resilient to external factors compared to centralized stablecoins.",
      },
      {
        question: "Where can I use Dai?",
        answer:
          "Dai can be used for payments, remittances, lending, and other decentralized finance (DeFi) applications on various platforms and protocols that support the Ethereum blockchain.",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: "uniswap",
    allTimeHigh: "44.97",
    moreInformation:
      "Uniswap (UNI) is a decentralized exchange (DEX) protocol built on the Ethereum blockchain. It allows users to trade cryptocurrencies directly from their wallets without the need for intermediaries or centralized exchanges. Uniswap utilizes automated market-making (AMM) algorithms to provide liquidity and enable seamless token swaps.",
    moreInformation2:
      "As a decentralized exchange protocol, Uniswap offers users high liquidity, low fees, and censorship-resistant trading. UNI tokens are used for governance, fee-sharing, and incentivizing liquidity providers on the platform.",
    frequentlyAskedQuestions: [
      {
        question: "What is Uniswap?",
        answer:
          "Uniswap (UNI) is a decentralized exchange (DEX) protocol that enables users to trade cryptocurrencies directly from their wallets without intermediaries.",
      },
      {
        question: "How does Uniswap work?",
        answer:
          "Uniswap utilizes automated market-making (AMM) algorithms and liquidity pools to facilitate token swaps and provide liquidity for various trading pairs on the platform.",
      },
      {
        question: "What are the benefits of using Uniswap?",
        answer:
          "Using Uniswap provides users with high liquidity, low fees, and censorship-resistant trading, as well as the ability to earn rewards through liquidity provision and governance participation.",
      },
    ],
  },
];
